We might not get seats?!
(Leonard:)It's fine, it's fine.
Go back to sleep.
Oh, I informed you thusly!
I so informed you thusly.
(Leonard:)Howard, you talk to him.
(Leonard:)Howard?
(Leonard:)You're peeing,
aren't you?
(Wil Wheaton:)Hey, look who's here!
(Wil Wheaton:)Hey, buddies!
(Sheldon:)Well, if it isn't Wil Wheaton,
the Jar Jar Binks
of the Star Trek universe.
Mee-sa think that very funny!
(Sheldon:)Well, you-sa can go think that
at the back of the line.
(Sheldon:)No cuts, no buts, no coconuts.
(Sheldon:)Wil Wheaton.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Theatre Staff:)I'm a big fan.
(Sheldon:)Of what? Poorly
executed beards?
(Wil:)Do you think you could get me
and my friends into the movie?
(Wil:)We got here
a little late.
(Theatre Staff:)No problem. Come on,
I'll hook you up.
(Wil:)Awesome.
(Wil:)We-sa gonna go into
the movie now! Bye-bye!
This is Indiana Jones,
not Star Trek.